{
    "subject": "Andrew_Lane",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Jake_Speed",
    "human_readable": "Andrew Lane directed Jake Speed.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8755212426185608,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Jake Speed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7411767244338989,
            "question": "Is Andrew Lane a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6548354029655457,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Andrew Lane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.649684727191925,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Jake Speed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6121900677680969,
            "question": "Was Jake Speed a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5920485854148865,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Andrew Lane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5351982712745667,
            "question": "What is known about the plot of Jake Speed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5291515588760376,
            "question": "When was the movie Jake Speed released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5142016410827637,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Jake Speed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42824968695640564,
            "question": "Where can I watch Jake Speed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andrew Lane directed Jake Speed.",
            "html": "yago_7308_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Jake Speed?",
            "html": "yago_7308_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the movie Jake Speed released?",
            "html": "yago_7308_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about the plot of Jake Speed?",
            "html": "yago_7308_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7308_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple is \"Andrew Lane directed Jake Speed.\"\n\nHere's the evaluation:\n\n* The context information mentions that Andrew Lane was an American film producer and director, and that he directed several films including Jake Speed. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7308/re-ranker-msmarco/51.txt)\n* Additionally, the same file (51.txt) mentions that Andrew Lane co-produced Jake Speed with Wayne Crawford.\n* Furthermore, another file (58.txt) states that Jake Speed was directed by Andrew Lane.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple \"Andrew Lane directed Jake Speed.\" Multiple sources indicate that Andrew Lane was indeed the director of the film Jake Speed, including the document `51.txt` which states, \"Together with Wayne Crawford he co-produced the 1983 comedy Valley Girl starring Nicolas Cage in his first co-starring role. [1] The two were responsible for producing several other films including Night of the Comet, Servants of Twilight, Mortal Passions, and Jake Speed.\" Another document `58.txt` also mentions that Jake Speed was directed by Andrew Lane."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}